《性爱大师》前情提要
Previously on "Masters of Sex"...
所以你认为你们之间的关系
So, you consider the relationship
有了更深层的意义吗
to have a higher purpose?
我们特殊的关系决定了我们
We are uniquely qualified
是找到治疗方法的最佳人选
to develop a treatment,
这能挽救不计其数的婚姻
to prevent countless marriages from dissolving.
我们不能标榜自己是
We cannot present ourselves
性功能障碍患者的救世主
as the saviors of the sexually dysfunctional
却仍未治愈一例病人
without having cured a single patient first,
包括我
including me.
或许你俩终究能指导全美国人
The two of you could finally teach America
如何做爱
how to have sex.
在电视上
On...television?
也不知道我为什么会有这种渴望
I don't know why I want what I want,
但如果你能
But if you would...
什么
What?
吻我
...kiss me,
或许我就能找出这一切答案
Then maybe I could figure it out.
我身体有些问题
I have a... a-a condition.
我跟女孩子做不了
I ca-- I can't do anything in the, uh...with a girl.
我  我身体也有问题
I-I also have a...condition,
我找到了份演出工作
I got a gig.
六个星期  为佛洛伊德·德索萨伴唱
Six weeks backing Floyd Desouza.
我们想带孩子们一起去
We want the kids to come, too.
去欧洲
To Europe?
为什么不行
Why not?
不行  我的回答是不行
No. My answer is no.
所以你情愿孩子们每天放学回来
So you would rather that they come home from school
却只能见到保姆吗
every day to a babysitter?
希望能晚点睡  这样才能见到妈妈
and hope that they can stay up late enough to see their mother.
如果你拒绝这件事
You see, you push back on this --
这个合理的请求
on a reasonable request --
你就是在自找麻烦
you could be opening up a whole can of worms.
我觉得你不会希望如此的
I don't think you want to do that.
性 爱 大 师
第二季 第十二集
人人影视
YYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
我觉得我们可能偶然发现了什么
I feel we may have stumbled upon something interesting.
那天晚上  摄制组离开后
That night, after the camera crew left,
那是我们第一次仅仅触摸彼此
that was the first time that we had ever touched --
翻译： 大师全勤草  暴龙蛋  王大可  叉烧包
■
仅仅是摸
just touched.
而没有隐含地把触摸当做性
Without the ulterior motive for touching being sex --
翻译：抹茶咖啡  Kiko  CS小明漫画家  教务长兔
甚至也没有试图去做爱
even an -- a-an attempt at sex.
还有那天晚上
And then that other night
时间轴：天羽  安妮  兜兜兜爹  后期：孤帆
你跟你弟弟发生争执之后
when you were so upset and vulnerable
十分难过  脆弱
after the fight with your brother,
校对：教务长兔  米小勒  总监：米小勒  教务长兔
■
我仅仅是通过抚摸你来安慰你
I comforted you just by touching you.
我当时也有能力来做爱了
And I was able to have sex.
鉴于以上
Given that...
我觉得我们应该换一个思路
I think we have to come at this with a different approach.
不做爱
Intercourse off the table,
但是触摸生殖器
but, also, the touching of genitals.
也不行
Also off the table.
只能进行与性无关的抚摸
Nonsexual touching only.
你绝对是性奋了
Well, you're definitely aroused.
或许我们现在应该试试
S-so maybe now is a good time to try.
那我们现在干什么
So...Now what?
如果我们加上摸生殖器这一项
All right, if -- if we put touching genitals back on the agenda...
但还是在真正做爱之前停下
But still stop before actual sex.
恩  不报有期望是关键
Right. No expectations being key.
这似乎是合理的下一步
That seems the logical next step.
我们现在知道性抚摸是有效的
We now know sexual touching works.
或许我们该继续进入真正做爱的部分
Maybe we should continue into actual sex.
我主动吧
Let me initiate first.
你就去感觉...
And you just feel -- feel...
感觉我
feel me.
感觉你自己的身体
Feel your body.
如果仔细看看我们的进展  还挺有意思的
It's interesting if you look at the progression.
七晚非性抚摸  多次勃起
Seven nights of nonsexual touching, multiple erections.
也有几次十足的灾难
With a few unmitigated disasters.
但还是不错了
But still.
然后又是七晚的性抚摸
And then followed by seven nights of sexual touching.
也是有多次勃起  如果不算上...
Again with multiple erections if you don't count --
是的  不算
I don't.
我们要关注结果中积极地一面
We're focusing on the positive.
现在我们又有几晚成功的...
And now we've had seven nights of successful...
而且是连续的
And successive...
是的  连续七晚成功性交了
Yes, seven nights of successive and successful coitus.
那么从这些结果来看
So based on these results,
到何时为止  可以认为你已经完全治愈了呢
at what point can we consider you cured?
经过了14年的公职磨砺
After 14 years on the national scene,
马萨诸塞州的约翰·F·肯尼迪参议员
Senator John F. Kennedy of Massachusetts,
经民主党选举  开始了总统竞选活动
selected by the Democratic Party, began his campaign for president,
展现出其之前寻求党内提名时同样的热情
showing the same enthusiasm he displayed while seeking the nomination.
你没关淋浴的水
You left the water on in the shower.
是吗
I did?
我真傻
How stupid of me.
我今天要去帮忙
I'm going in today to volunteer.
去种族平等协会吗
At C.O.R.E.?
我以为你不去了
I thought you'd given that up.
他们领导层之前去了亚特兰大
The leadership has been in Atlanta,
抗议金博士的逮捕
protesting the arrest of Dr. King.
他们今天回来了  我还是会继续去的
They're back today, and, no, I have not given it up.
你妈妈很快就会来了  照看孩子们
Your mother should be here soon to stay with the children.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你们两个
I love you both so much, hmm?
我好爱你们
So, so much.
你们不知道我有多爱你们
You have no idea.
太好了
Oh. Good.
布拉多克老师迟到了
Miss Braddock is running late.
其实  你迟到了
Actually, you're late.
布拉多克老师准时到了
Miss Braddock's on time.
所以她叫其他家长进去了
That's why she took the other parents in --
因为他们已经到了
the ones who were already here.
那他们一定是早到了
Well, they must've been early --
一定是想给布拉多克老师留个好印象
Trying to impress miss Braddock, no doubt.
早到有什么不好吗
Well, would that be such a bad thing?
我看过亨利上一张成绩卡
I did see Henry's last report card.
昨天  约翰尼·J给我来电话了
Hey, I got a call from Johnnie J. yesterday.
他说要让我常驻大都市俱乐部那里演出
He offered me a regular gig at the cosmopolitan club.
圣约翰三人组现在每晚在那儿表演四天
St. John's trio is now playing there four nights a week.
先是欧洲  又是圣路易斯
First Europe and now St. Louis.
我一直在想
I've been thinking...
孩子可不可以平时多去
What if the kids, uh, spent a little more time
我家待几天
at my place during the week?
不再是每周一晚  或许增加到两三晚呢
Instead of just the one night, maybe two or even three?
你才带他们去欧洲待了六周而已
You just had them for six weeks in Europe.
是啊  而且我从没见过他们那么开心的样子
Yeah, and I've never seen them happier.
那是因为你们很少见面
Well, that's because you hardly ever see them.
吉妮  我就是想改变这一点
My point, Gin, is to change that.
我要说的重点是
And my point is
别让我后悔曾向你让过步  乔治
don't make me regret giving you an inch, George.
真是的  你这都哪来的念头啊
I mean, seriously. Where is this all coming from?
奥黛丽吗
Audrey?
我为什么就不能改变了呢
Why can't I have changed?
你人是改变了  为了奥黛丽
You have changed -- changed for Audrey.
虽然我很高兴这过去的六个月里
And while I'm so pleased that she has managed to
她让你知道了如何做个父亲
acquaint you with fatherhood in these past six months,
别忘了我才是一直守在他们身边的人
Let's not forget I'm the one who has been here for them
自始至终  参加家长会
since the beginning -- all of the conferences
假日出去  还有他们生病时
and the vacations and the sleepless nights
那些不眠夜
when they've been sick and --
好啊  但也别忘了
Fine, okay, but let's not forget
作为家长  你自己也有不是
that you've had your own problems in the parent department.
我们要实话实说  对吧
I mean, we're being honest, right?
我们两个都不是很好的家长  吉妮
Neither of us is particularly great parent material, Gin.
你知道谁是吗  奥黛丽
But you know who is? Audrey.
她很爱两个孩子
No, she loves the kids.
她陪他们的时间比我们俩加起来都长
And she spends more time with them than either of us put together.
难道孩子们不该有一个把他们放在第一的
And don't our kids deserve to have at least one parent
家长吗
who puts them first?
得了吧  我就装作我没听到那些话
No, I-I am going to pretend that I didn't hear that.
事实上  我今天就是想说给你听
Well, actually, I want you to hear it.
不  乔治
No, George.
你可以继续每周带一次孩子
You can have our kids once a week like always,
就像我们说好的那样
as we've agreed.
虽然今晚该你带孩子
And while it is your night tonight,
但你刚刚跟他们待了六周
you did just have them for six weeks,
所以我今晚就把他们留在家里了
so I'm going to keep them at home with me tonight.
这算什么  惩罚我提出一个可能对孩子们
What's that, a punishment for suggesting something that might
-有好处的提议吗  -布拉多克老师
- actually be good for the kids? - Miss Braddock!
约翰逊的家长来了
The Johnsons are here.
我不需要纸巾  谢谢
Oh, I-I don't need tissues, thank you.
其实是件小事
This is, uh, it's a small matter really.
你也知道  我跟我前夫乔治
As you know, I share custody of my children
对我们的孩子有共同抚养权
with my ex-husband, George.
欧洲之旅如何呀
Oh, h-how was the European tour?
挺好的吧
Fine, I suppose.
我来是因为我当初跟他离婚的时候
But I'm here because I-I may have been a bit sloppy
可能有些大意了
when I dissolved our marriage.
大意
Sloppy?
是的  乔治根本就不想要孩子
Yes, you see, George never even wanted children --
从来就是这样
Not even from the beginning.
所以到了签署监护权协议的时候
And so when it came time to finalize a custody agreement --
你手上没有签过字的协议
You don't have a signed one.
我当时觉得没这个必要
Well, I-it just -- it seemed irrelevant at the time.
但现在他皈依耶稣了呗
But now he's found Jesus.
其实是奥黛丽
Audrey.
我的意思是  如果有律师去跟他交涉
My point is, George will back off quickly enough
乔治马上就会退缩
when he's confronted with an actual lawyer,
我觉得如今又出现了新的妻子
which I do think is important
这一点就格外重要了
now that there is a new wife in the picture.
新妻子就像钫
New wives are like francium --
是最不稳定的元素
the most unstable of all the elements.
你还涉足化学吗
You dabble in chemistry?
是这样  在另一种生活中
Eh, in another life.
在那种生活中我认为宇宙是有秩序的
A life where I thought there was order to the universe.
现在我更清楚了
Now I know better.
协议就交给我去帮你办吧
So now I get contracts signed.
在中西部地区的中心
In the heart of the midwest,
密苏里河的河畔上
along the banks of the Missouri river,
座落着一颗闪耀的明星  圣易路斯市
lies the sparkling city of St. Louis.
这座人口达二十五万...
With a quarter of a million people living...
这是给圣路易斯旅游局做的吗
Is this for the St. Louis tourist board?
我想这应该是正片前的铺垫吧
I'm sure they're just setting the stage.
这个创意旨在帮助观众
The idea was to ease the audience
进入主题
into the subject matter.
这里高楼林立  堆砌起一个繁荣的社会
There are many building blocks to a prosperous society,
但其中一个主要的元素就是婚姻
but one essential element is marriage.
男女之间那种牢固  幸福的联结
A strong, happy union between a man and a woman
无论对家庭还是整个社区
is crucial to both the family unit
都至关重要
and to the community at large.
但如何使婚姻幸福呢
But what makes a happy marriage?
为解答这个问题  我们先看看
To answer the question, what kind of changes occur
夫妻生活中身体都发生了怎样的变化
physically during moments of marital intimacy?
我想这句话的表达方式应该是...
I think I phrased it,
"性交时身体发生了怎样的变化"
"What happens to the body during sex?"
人们都是有经验的
Well, people are sophisticated.
-听得懂话外音  -在观察性反应过程中
- They'll read between the lines. - Sexual response.
我们发现了许多生理现象
And where we observed, uh, many physical phenomenon.
例如男女的心率都会加速
An accelerated heart rate in both men and women.
呼吸频率也会加快  汗也会出得更多
Respiration also increased, as did perspiration.
实验对象双方的皮肤都会持续泛起潮红
There's a consistent skin flush in both subjects
我们称之为血管充血
called vasocongestion.
我确定我说的是"男女方皮肤都会出现潮红"
I'm fairly certain I said "Skin flush in both sexes."
没错  但台里更喜欢"实验对象"这个词儿
You did, but the network preferred the word "Subjects."
我们用你另一段采访剪辑了一下
Uh, we looped it from another part of your interview.
男女双方
And in both men and women,
血压都会明显增高
there is a marked increase in blood pressure.
跟心脏病的症状一样
All the symptoms of a heart attack.
是的  但我们现在说的是性
Yes, but here, we're talking about sex.
我的错
I must've missed that.
研究会继续在美国的中心地区进行
The study continues here in America's heartland,
因为马斯特斯和约翰逊现在将要在
as Masters and Johnson are now poised to break new ground
身体功能障碍的治疗上开创一片新天地
in the treatment of physical dysfunction.
身体功能障碍
Physical dysfunction.
它可以是指...
It could imply...
痛风或截肢
Gout or amputation.
因为我们都知道
Because we see the couple
那些夫妻去找你的原因  比尔
going into your offices, Bill, we know the context.
障碍指的就是性功能
The dysfunction is sexual.
我们最主要的目标就是
Our goal, first and foremost,
增进理解  让人们敢于开口谈论
is to promote understanding, to start a dialogue
那些长期被认为是禁忌的话题
about a subject long considered taboo.
好了  那些只是粗剪的片段
Okay, well, that's just a rough cut,
给你们看看大致的轮廓
but it gives you the general layout of the piece.
CBS电视台非常高兴
Now, CBS is very pleased.
这个故事是史无前例的
No one else has a story like it.
而且我感觉现在也是时候了
And I feel it's not a moment too soon.
我调查过你们加大的约瑟夫·考夫曼医生
I did some more digging into your, uh, Dr. Joseph Kaufman
原来他也正要出版自己的研究
at U.C.L.A., and it turns out he is publishing his work,
叫什么"人与性"
something called "Man And Sex."
出版给大众的书吗
A book for general publication?
还有两个月才出版
Publication is two months away.
所以我们要用这个影片赶在他们前面
Now, we're gonna be out there first with this,
就像我所说的  一旦你们的领域确立
and as I've said, once you've marked your territory,
其他人再来研究就像是在炒剩饭
the next guy to come along often looks like yesterday's news.
但也并非总是如此吧
But not always?
不用担心
N-not to worry.
一旦这部电影播出  媒体就会接踵而至
Once the film airs, there's gonna be follow-up press.
访谈和简介层出不穷
There's gonna be interviews and profiles.
我们的形式一片大好
We're in great shape.
圣路易斯的关注会有所下降
By taking the focus off St. Louis,
我们现在必须重新动员基层力量
we now have to re-energize our base.
就好像我们淡出公众视线了几个月
Like we out of sight for a few months,
突然就被大家遗忘了
and suddenly we're out of mind.
欢迎回来
Welcome home.
很高兴你来了
Glad you came in.
我们回来工作了
We're, uh, back to work, obviously.
你可以来搭把手
We can use an extra pair of hands.
我们正给居屋委员会的所有人
We're, uh, sending a letter of intent to everyone
发一份意向书
on the housing board.
需要有人来填写地址贴邮票
The envelopes need to be addressed and stamped.
我可以做
I can do that.
格伦  你去给马斯特斯夫人准备油印件
Glenn, go and get Mrs. Masters settled by the mimeo.
曼尼  你陪我去给负责人德雷克打电话
Manny, I want you with me when I call supervisor Drake.
那些对我们工作的简述
A presentation of our work
又把性爱推回到了封闭之中
that puts sex back in the closet.
我也知道那不能称为美化用词
I'm not saying that it wasn't sanitized.
那跟个牙膏广告似的
It had all the gravitas of a toothpaste commercial!
也没有那么具体啦
It wasn't specific.
但谢普所说得有道理...
But Shep's point, which is well-taken --
我还跟谢普说了
I also told Shep to take out that reference
不要提性功能障碍这一段
to sexual dysfunction,
但影片里还有  的确违背了我们的初衷
yet there it was anyway, against our wishes.
什么身体功能障碍
Physical dysfunction,
可我们在那方面也没约法三章过
and we made no promises in that regard.
弗吉尼娅  你到底帮谁啊
Virginia, stop defending the indefensible.
我们自己都还没完全攻克功能障碍这方面
We barely have a handle on dysfunction ourselves,
更别说什么真实患者统计上的成功
let alone any statistical success with actual subjects --
除了我自己
other than me.
这是一个新研究
This is -- this is new work
目前还处于一种微妙和脆弱的局面
in, uh, a delicate and fragile state.
研究是指...
The work is?
还是说我们讨论的是另外一件事
Or...Are we talking about something else?
听着  如果我们真的发现
look, if we have found something as --
一种确切的治疗手段
as radical as this appears to be,
能治疗像阳痿这样棘手的疑难杂症
to -- to -- to fix something as intractable as impotence,
你首先得把注意力从性上移开
you first turn the focus entirely away from sex.
是啊  那将会是开创性的...
Yeah, and that would be groundbreaking and --
是的  没错
Yes, it would be.
所以它不能被破坏
So it cannot be jeopardized.
你说得对
You're right.
我们离对外发表还远得很
We are nowhere near publishing.
但那个洛杉矶医生的书就快出版了
But that doctor in Los Angeles, he is.
如果他的书引起了公众的兴趣
And if his book happens to catch the public's fancy
我们就彻底地被踢出这个圈子了
and we are cut out of the discussion entirely...
比尔  我同意你的看法
Bill, I agree with you.
我知道那部电影不尽人意
I know that the film is not ideal,
但被彻底地踢出圈子  那样更糟
but being cut out completely, that is worse!
电影一经播出
The film will air.
会有百万的观众看到  他们会说
Millions of people will watch, and they will say,
"这就是性研究者马斯特斯和约翰逊"
"yes, Masters and Johnson, the sex researchers."
谁知道呢  也许我们从此就家喻户晓了
Who knows? Maybe we'll even become household names.
之后当我们已经准备好用自己的方法
And then when we are ready to present our work
来呈现我们的研究
and do it our way,
那时我们已经有观众
there will already be an audience
准备好并愿意接受我们了
that is ready and willing to take us seriously.
史普利博先生  请坐
Oh. Mr. Spleeb, please, have a seat.
不用了
Oh, no. That won't be necessary.
我跟你丈夫乔治谈过了
I had a chat with husband George.
是前夫
Ex-husband.
非常感谢
and thank you so much.
还没签啊
It's not signed.
乔治不想签
George wasn't in the signing mood.
我没听懂你的意思
I'm not sure... I know what you mean.
乔治不仅...
Well, not only will george
不愿签你的原始抚养协议
not sign your original custody agreement,
他还给自己请了位律师
he has retained an attorney of his own.
听着  我不知道你有什么困扰
Look, I don't know what's bothering you,
但别把你的卧室问题赖在我的头上
but don't take your bedroom problems out on me.
我没有什么卧室问题
I have no bedroom problems.
我的卧室里没有什么困扰着我
There's nothing in my bedroom that bothers me!
那可真是太糟了
Ohh, that's too bad.
搞得我们好像不知道结局似的
It's not like we don't all know how it's gonna end.
然后按照既定框架有条不紊地演着...
...And -- and work out some sort of schedule...
男孩爱上女孩  女孩爱上男孩
Guy falls in love with girl, girl falls in love with guy,
然后过着幸福的生活
Complications develop hilarity ensues,
真爱战胜一切  演职人员表
Love conquers all, roll credits.
现在  从整点到半点  电话会...
Now, from the hour to the half-hour, the phone...
这又浪费了我们两个小时的生命
That's two hours of our lives we'll never get back.
我喜欢啊
I-I liked it.
我觉得很好笑也很聪明
I-I thought it was funny and very clever.
艺术不应该是聪明的
Art's not supposed to be clever.
应该是真实的  像生活一样真实
It's supposed to be true -- true to life.
在生活中  你没办法通过打电话和
In real life, you can't fix bedroom problems
重新装修公寓解决卧室里那些问题
by calling up a party line and redecorating an apartment.
我知道  我只是
I know that. I just...
想忘记一晚上现实生活
wanted to forget real life for an evening, anyway.
我忘不了  一秒钟都忘不了
Well, I can't forget -- not even for a second.
因为我看着你  我就想
It's because I look at you, and I think...
我应该找个像你一样美丽甜美的女孩
I should sweep a girl as pretty and as sweet --
我应该让你为我神魂颠倒
I should sweep you off your feet...
而不是像个残废一样站在这里
not just stand here like a-a cripple.
但你知道我也是有缺陷的
But you know I'm crippled, too.
不  没事的
No, it's okay.
你有什么问题我都接受
I-I accept you no matter what problems --
我也接受你  莱斯特
I-I accept you, too, Lester.
如果你是想说你因为
If -- if you're saying that you're upset
我们不能  那个什么  而感到沮丧
because we can't, you know, do that...
我就是因为我们不可以那什么而沮丧
I am upset because we can't do that.
那我们就做好了
Well, then let's do this.
什么
What?
我们可以看些电影
Uh, w-we -- we can go see movies.
或者玩我们都喜欢的拼字游戏
Or -- or we could play scrabble, which we both love.
我们可以去跳舞
We could go out dancing.
也许我们甚至可以
Maybe we could even...
睡在一起
sleep together.
不  芭布  我是说  我们  我不行
No, Barb. I'm telling you, we -- I can't --
我知道  我的意思是只是  睡觉
I know. I-I mean just...sleep.
当我们公开承认了
When we admitted publicly
U-2[秘密侦查机]属于我们
that the U-2 belonged to us...
看起来某些人很有食欲
Looks like someone worked up an appetite.
我没吃午饭
I missed lunch.
我们在现代社会做着一些事情
We were doing something that in a modern world...
我发誓  给他贴上胡子
I swear, slap a beard on him,
他一定很像时光老人
he's a dead ringer for father time.
周五来  那时我们就会有个
Come friday, we'll have a president
头发茂密的总统了
with a full head of hair.
这对我来说可是第一次
That's a first in my lifetime.
当我第一次看到杰姬时
When I first saw a picture of Jackie,
我心想  我总算知道什么叫做美国梦了
I thought, "Now I know what the american dream is."
那约翰·肯尼迪呢
And John Kennedy?
他就在上演美国梦
He is living it.
我在小学当过主席
I was junior class president.
那是我人生最美好的一年
Um, best year of my life.
但我们也有个恶心的就职典礼
But we also had a hell of an inauguration.
显然真正的就职典礼
Well, the real one's gonna be buried
会被淹没在厚厚的积雪中了
under a foot of snow apparently.
我会多带一副耳罩的
I'm bringing an extra pair of earmuffs
以防第一副冻坏
in case the first pair freezes.
你要去就职典礼吗
You're going to the inauguration?
这倒提醒我了
That reminds me,
我周五走后需要你留守在办公室
I need you to man the office on friday while I'm out.
你知道在电视上看
You do know you get a much better view
视角更好吧
on television, don't you?
我家里人能搞到好位子
My family has good seats.
他们在谴责美国
That they are condemning the United States...
我的弟弟在为新班子工作
My kid brother's working for the new administration.
是吗
yeah.
鲍比疏通了关系  在司法部门给他找了工作
Bobby pulled some strings, got him a job in justice.
但是如果不是我父亲
Although, without my father,
肯尼迪肯定赢不下密苏里州
Kennedy never would've won Missouri at all.
选总统可不便宜
It's not cheap running for president,
我爸爸知道该去疏通哪些人
and daddy knows exactly whose hands need greasing.
如果不懂些零售政治
You don't go from being an immigrant pickle peddler
你没法从一个一句英语都不懂的
who can't speak a lick of english
移民泡菜小贩做到
to owning the biggest hardware chain in the midwest
拥有中西部最大的五金连锁店
without learning something about retail politics.
是哪家五金店
Hardware as in...
帕克五金
Packer Hardware.
等等  你就是那个帕克吗
Wait. Th-- you're that Packer?
你要知道我被拉去参加了多少个
If you knew how many of these fundraising dinners
募款晚宴啊
I've been dragged to...
还有明晚的那个宴会
And this party tomorrow night.
在圣路易斯的宴会么
There -- a party here in St. Louis?
是啊  密苏里州民主党的盛大宴会
Yeah, a big shindig for The Democratic Party of Missouri.
所有那些州长和议员聚集一堂
All those governors and senators in the same place...
都能让鲨鱼睡着了
It's enough to make a shark sleep.
为一个不同的世界努力
And work for a different kind of world.
威廉·马斯特斯
我想要
Uh, well, what I'm asking,
请你帮忙
I-I suppose, is, uh, a favor.
泌尿科的约瑟夫·科夫曼医生
A Dr. Joseph Kaufman, uh, in urology,
他正要出版一本书
he's publishing a book.
叫做"人与性"
It's called "Man And Sex."
很显然就在几个月之内
In a couple months, apparently.
是啊  你也能想象到
Yes. Well, you can imagine.
我也
I'd also --
你能那样做吗
Y-you could do that?
那就太感激了
well, I-I would be most grateful.
我会的
I would.
说实话  我想要道歉
Honestly, I-I wanted to apologize.
因为派了个律师去我家吗
For sending a lawyer to my house.
是的  那很
Yes. That was...
-您的饮料  -谢谢
- Your drink. - Thank you.
那有些反应过度了
It was an overreaction.
最近工作上  太忙碌了
I -- the situation at work has been, um, so taxing.
我  我很疲惫  我
I was -- I was exhausted, and I, uh...
你反应过度了
You overreacted.
是的
Yes.
所以
So...
你想与孩子们更多的接触
You want to spend more time with the kids.
所以让我们好好谈谈
So let's talk about what might make sense.
我认为应该是律师来谈
I think our lawyers should talk.
我没有律师
I don't have a lawyer.
不  史普利博先生是
No, Mr. Spleeb is --
他只是在我们办公室工作而已
He's just somebody who works in our offices, that's all.
我想你肯定
I don't think
不愿意在没有律师的情况下上法庭
you want to walk into court unrepresented.
如果我们能自己解决问题的话
Why...would I walk into court at all
我为什么要上法庭呢
when we can just sort this out ourselves?
因为奥黛丽和我聊过了
Well, because Audrey and I have been talking.
说实话  我觉得每周多一天就够了
And, honest, I thought one more day a week would be enough.
但当你真的认真考虑的时候
But when you really think about it,
孩子们需要知道哪里是家
the kids have to know where home is.
亨利和泰莎知道
Henry and Tessa do know.
就是和我在一起
It's with me.
是的  当你在的时候
Yeah, when you're there.
这种情况又有多少时间呢
But how often is that?
我想要一个法官在公开法庭上
I want a judge in open court
听听我们的孩子是如何度过每一天的
to hear a typical day for our kids.
我需要一个关于你在做的事情的
I want an impartial opinion about
公平的意见
what it is you're doing.
是不是有些人告诉你了一些
Has someone, uh, been, uh, telling you
关于我工作的荒唐谎言
some ridiculous lie about my hours?
孩子告诉我的
The kids tell me.
他们不再是孩子了
They're not babies anymore.
他们知道你什么时候回来和离开
They know when you come and go.
我必须从他们的利益出发  吉妮
I have to think about what's best for them now, Gin.
我的律师也很清楚
And my lawyer was crystal-clear,
考虑到法庭对父亲的偏见
given the court's bias against fathers,
如果我们想赢得任何对我有利的和解
if we hope to win any sort of settlement in my favor
我们必须在法庭展现出
with the kids, then we have to show the court that you're...
你不称职
that you're unfit.
我没有不称职
Un-- I'm not unfit.
听着  如果希望改变现状
Look, if the situation is gonna change --
我会重新安排我的时间
I-I'll rearrange my schedule!
不仅仅是时间的问题
It's...not just the schedule.
必须要在法庭
It's gonna come up in court...
在法官面前
in front of the judge.
你实际上在观察人们私通这件事
The fact...that you watch people fornicating.
私通
Fornicating?
做爱
Fucking.
还有你和你的老板有外遇
That you're having an affair with your boss.
什么
W-what?!
不然为什么你一周总有两个晚上
Well, how else do you explain that two nights a week,
会因为工作半夜才回家
you don't get home until midnight because you're working?
人们听到这个还能怎么想
What's anyone supposed to think hearing that?
你意识到自己在说什么吗
Do you even realize what it is you're saying?
我当然知道
Of course I realize it.
你是说你会通过曝光这件事
You're saying that you would take my kids,
来抢走我的孩子
that you would discredit me,
来诋毁我的名誉
that you would discredit my work
和我的工作
by dragging this into public?
看到了吧  这就是问题所在
Yeah, see? And there it is.
你并不是真正在关心孩子们  吉妮
You're not really worried about the kids, Gin.
你只担心你的研究
It's that study that you're worried about.
这顿我请
It's my treat.
你可以去里面换衣服
Uh, you can change in there for, uh, privacy.
毛巾是干净的
And clean towels.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
那个...门还开着
Oh, the -- the door is still open.
谢谢
Thanks.
那个  它们...
Okay, so, they, uh --
它们有点大
They're a little big.
我们要不要...
Um, should we -- uh, yeah.
我还有别的枕头
I have other pillows.
不用不用  这样就很好
Oh, no, no, no, no. These -- these are perfect.
晚安  莱斯特
Good night, Lester.
晚安
Good night.
说实话
I'll be honest.
我不习惯在凌晨两点招待客人
I'm not used to having guests at 2:00 in the morning.
希望没吵醒寇儿
I hope I didn't wake Coral.
没有  寇儿还在亚特兰大
No, uh, Coral's still in Atlanta.
她坚持要去  坚持要待在那里
Yeah, she insisted on going and insisted on staying.
她现在全心全意致力于工作了
She's real committed to the work now.
我很为她感到骄傲
I'm...really proud of her.
真了不起
It's very impressive.
还是要抱歉这么晚过来
Uh, I do apologize for the hour.
不必的  真的
You know, don't, really.
实际上  我才应该道歉
In fact, uh, I'm the one who should be apologizing.
我知道
Well, at work,
在工作上你要保证专业形象
I know you need to maintain a certain professionalism.
我是说
I mean, I'm, uh...
我为那晚在你家的事感到抱歉
sorry about that night... at your house.
我不知道你什么意思
I'm not sure what you mean.
我不知道自己为什么会让那件事发生
I'm not sure why I let it happen.
那件事
"It"?
那种事不是你能掌控的
It wasn't something that you let --
它能被掌控
But it was.
是可以的  而现在
It was, and now...
我要为此负责
I need to take responsibility for that.
那是非常鲁莽
It was -- it was reckless,
危险  甚至是背叛的行为
dangerous, and a betrayal, even.
和我们努力经营的一切背道而驰
Goes against everything we're working so hard for.
我们  你是说种族平等协会啊
"We're"? Oh, you mean C.O.R.E.
如果我要真实地面对自己
And if I'm real honest with myself,
我之所以这样做  大概就是因为
well, it may even be why I did it --
它充满危险
the danger of it.
一个和我完全不是一个世界的女人
A woman so outside my world.
或许我内心深处
Maybe a part of me
依然渴望着往那个橱窗上扔砖头
still wants to throw a brick through that window.
我也不知道
I don't really know.
我不会再来这里了
I won't come here again.
-我很抱歉  -别再说这句话了
- I am sorry. - Stop saying that!
如果你这样做是因为你想要我呢
What if you did it because you wanted me?
如果这才是真正的原因呢
What if that was the reason?
请问是哪位找
Okay, but who's askin'?
好的  请等一下
Oh, all right, then. Hold on a moment, please.
休·海夫纳先生打电话来
Uh, Mr. Hugh Hefner is on the line.
想和你聊两句
Would like a moment of your time.
《花花公子》杂志的休·海夫纳吗
Hugh Hefner from Playboy magazine?
没错  长耳朵  蓬松白尾巴的兔女郎老板
Mm, little ears, fluffy white tail.
让他先留个口信
Take a message, please.
莱斯特  能和你说句话吗
Lester, can I see you a moment?
我没兴趣
I'm not interested.
我能理解你有些犹豫
I understand your hesitancy,
考虑到事情的进展不那么顺利
given that things didn't go particularly smoothly.
-和那个妓女吗  -这次不一样
- With the hooker? - This is different.
你有治愈阳痿的方法了吗
You have a cure... for impotence?
我没说能治愈
I didn't say a cure.
但可能会是一个治疗方案或是
But perhaps the beginnings of a protocol
疗法的开端
a-a treatment.
我现在有女朋友了
Well, I have a girlfriend.
女朋...
A...
芭布
Barb.
芭芭拉·桑德森  另一个失败的试验对象
Barbara Sanderson -- one of the other failed experiments.
这么说  你们俩
So -- so you two have --
可以成功地进行性行为吗
have been able to engage in...successful sex?
我们不需要
We don't need to.
我们有新的方式  我们可以相互做伴
We've found a new way. We can be together.
完全没有性行为  我们也可以很快乐
We can be happy...by removing sex from the equation entirely.
这不是个永久的解决方案
Well, not as a-a permanent solution.
这根本不是解决方案
That -- that would be no solution at all.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因为你...
Because you...
你多大了
How old are you?
29岁
I'm 29.
我不是个孩子了
I'm not a kid.
我能理解  人这一生
I understand you don't get
不可能总是得其所求
everything you want in this life.
我们不是在讨论一辆凯迪拉克  莱斯特
We're not talking about a cadillac, Lester.
你们这样不可能维持下去的
You wouldn't be able to sustain it.
一场没有浪漫行为的浪漫恋爱关系
A romantic relationship with no romance?
我们有很多浪漫行为
We have plenty of romance.
没有性行为的恋爱关系...
A relationship with no sex...
性行为就像呼吸和吃饭一样是基本需求
Sex is as basic as breathing, eating.
你整个人最终都会有所反抗的
Your entire being will eventually rebel.
艾萨克·牛顿发明了很多微积分算法
Isaac Newton invented a lot of calculus.
但是他完全没有性生活
He had no sex at all.
他是自己选择要做一辈子处男
Well, he was a virgin by choice.
除非你能想出
And unless you're coming up
下一条万有引力定律
with the next law of universal gravitation,
否则最终  你会意识到
eventually, you're going to realize
你不会愿意一生无性的
you do not want to live without this.
芭芭拉最终也会这么想
And Barbara is gonna come to the same conclusion.
相信我
Trust me.
我知道我以前就让你相信我
I've asked you to trust me before, I know.
但是这次不同
But this time is different.
我是希望你能考虑...
I'm asking you to consider...
一种新的方法
a new way.
你期待今晚的聚会吗
Are you excited about the party tonight?
简直要激动死了
Over the moon.
我晚上八点在体育俱乐部
Listen, I have a weekly poker game
有每周一次的牌局
at the Athletic Club at 8:00.
每次都能大赚一笔
It's always a lucrative evening.
但是我一直在想  你得独自一人
But I've been thinking about you going
去参加这场无聊的政治聚会
to this boring political thing
没有男伴的陪同
all by yourself without a date.
虽然  我们之间并不是传统的恋爱关系
Obviously, we don't have a conventional relationship,
但是我喜欢你
but I am fond of you.
我是想说
Well, what I'm saying is
如果你今晚需要我去
if you need me to be there tonight --
需要我陪你去
to -- to be there for you...
那好吧
Okeydoke.
你是说我应该去吗
Are you saying I should come?
不是
No.
你已经有男伴了
Oh. You already have a date.
没有
No.
那我就不明白了
Then I-I...I don't understand.
我的家人  他们可不是一般人
My family -- they're not like other families.
我见他们前一周
A week before I see them,
还得每天早上阅读《纽约时报》
I have to read "The New York Times" every morning
从头看到尾  好像备考一样
Cover to cover like I'm studying for a test.
我的一个哥哥是律师
I have one brother who's a lawyer,
一个哥哥是
One brother who --
他说是为政府工作
well, he says he works for the government.
很有可能是中央情报局的
He's probably C.I.A.
另一个如今是新一届政府班子
The other's now working for the new administration,
所以我们才得参加今晚的宴会
hence this evening.
你想说什么
Your point being what?
你是不是在暗示  以我的智商
Because if you're implying that I can't keep up...
跟不上他们的话题
you know, intellectually...
提醒你一下  我是医学院毕业的
Let me remind you I went to medical school.
我还是博士
I am also a doctor.
读医的大部分出来都是博士吧
One does tend to lead to the other.
我对公众事务也很感兴趣
I am also very interested in public affairs.
甚至曾经考虑过投身政界
I've even considered going into politics myself.
真的吗
Really?
这我还真没看出来
I didn't know that about you.
那么北约形成的真正原因是什么
So, why was NATO really formed,
除了遏制苏联扩张之外
aside from being an attempt to rein in Soviet aggression?
谁会在聚会上问这种问题
I mean, who would ask that at a party?
你该不是觉得我拿不出手吧
I mean, you cannot be embarrassed by me.
以我的外表  怎么可能
That -- that is physically impossible.
我可没说"拿不出手"
I didn't say "Embarrassed."
可你确实这么想的  是不是
But you are, aren't you?
你
Well...You...
让我弄明白
Let me get this...straight.
你天天缠着我  就像我是你的种马似的
You run me around like I'm your personal inseminator,
可却不让我见家人
But when it comes to me meeting your family?
亲爱的  不是你的问题  是他们
Honey, it's not you. It's them.
他们会撇你一眼说
They'll take one look at you and say,
他的头发可真是  金光闪闪
"Wow. He really is...Blond."
你是在说我金发无脑
Are you calling me a dumb blond?!
奥斯丁  拜托
Austin. Please.
你这种颜色的头发  可是许多女人梦寐以求的
Women pay a lot of money for that color in a hair salon.
所以当然  我正跟我的律师沟通
So, of course, I'm talking to my attorney,
他也在跟乔治的律师沟通
who's talking to George's attorney.
但事实上  我可能必须辞职了
But...the truth is, I might have to quit.
-你真要辞职吗  -我
- Would you really quit? - I...
-你告诉比尔了吗  -没有
- Have you told bill? - No. No.
我什么都没说  我正在想办法解决
I haven't said anything. I'm trying to figure this out.
但我唯一的选择可能只有辞职
But my only option may be to quit.
可就算你辞了职
But even if you quit,
乔治就不会跟你闹上法庭了吗
won't george still take you to court?
他还是会
Yes, he will.
但他就不能
But he won't be able to
拿我的工作说事了
hold the work over my head any longer.
他的律师就不会说了吗
Won't his lawyer?
我是说  他的律师可能会说
I mean, won't his lawyer say
这么多年你来你都在做这个工作
you've been doing this work all these years,
而现在你辞职了
and you've only now just quit
只是为了在法官面前好看点
to make it look better to a Judge?
我不是泼你凉水
I don't say that to be discouraging.
-我只是  万一如此  -我懂
- I just...in case... - I know.
我必须想办法跟他斗  我
I-I have to fight him somehow. I-I...
我会想到办法的
I-I-I will think of something.
我禁不住想如果比尔对我这么做
I'm just imagining if Bill did this to me --
要夺走我的孩子
tried to take my kids.
我漂亮  完美的宝贝  我
My beautiful, perfect children, whom I...
无比珍爱  宝贝的他们  那真是
love and adore beyond reason. It's...
可是这两个孩子
And yet, those children --
当我想到  他们可能就是我的全部时
when I think that they may be all that there is for me,
这还不够
it's not enough.
他们不能是我生命的全部
They cannot be the only thing --
如果失去了仅有的他们  我会死的
Just them and only them, or I will -- I will die.
就算不是真的死去  至少心灵上...
If not literally, then at least --
莉比
Lib.
是不是发生了什么事
Has something happened?
如果
What if...
如果放弃这一切
God, what if you just let go
你以为属于自己的生活会如何
of everything that you thought your life would be?
如果你我都这么做
What if we both did?
那又会怎么样呢
Just -- what then?
那可是我的孩子啊
It's my children.
我知道  他们是你的孩子   但是
I know they are. They are. But...
当你考虑孩子时  到底是什么让你放不下
What really matters when you think about your children?
不是《女性挚友》封面说的那一套
No, not something on the cover of Woman's Day,
在你内心深处到底是怎么想的
But -- but deep down.
他们的安全
T-t-they're safe.
我也不知道
I don't know.
他们的幸福
That they're -- that they're happy
他们能感受到自己是被爱的
And that they know -- they know that they're loved.
也许这就是关键
Maybe that's the key --
放下那些理想
to let go of some...ideal.
去经营你真实的生活
To live the life that you have,
而不是沉醉在你认为自己该有的生活中
not the life that you thought you would have.
去接受
To finally...
真正的生活
just accept what is.
《男人与性》  未校订
我要走了
I'm gonna be heading out.
这就是装在绝密信封里的东西
Hmm. That was in the top-secret envelope?
没有寄出或者寄入的地址
No address to or from.
送它过来的小子也不肯说是谁让送的
The kid that delivered it wouldn't say who sent him.
所以我想这不是原子弹设计蓝图
So, uh, I figure it's either a blueprint for the A-bomb,
就是杰姬送来的总统就职典礼邀请函
or a Jackie sent in a personal invite to the swearing-in.
这是
It's, uh...
我们的竞争对手
It's our competition...
加州大学洛杉矶分校的那个博士
The doctor at U.C.L.A..
这是他写的书
This is his book.
特别引人入胜吗
A real page-turner?
内容不多  也不深奥
It's thin, conversational.
写给外行看的
It's written for the layman.
没有复杂的科学知识
Not much science.
没有数据注释  其实几乎没有数据
No annotating of data -- hardly any data at all.
听起来更像是消遣读物
Hmm, more like summer reading.
就像我们拍的片子
More like our film.
可是我们的研究  我们真正的研究
Whereas our work -- our real work --
远不是科夫曼医生所能及
is miles beyond Dr. Kaufman's.
我们的研究  会让卡夫曼医生被世人所遗忘
Our work...will leave Dr. Kaufman in the dust.
听着
Look.
我以前总会取笑
I used to poke fun at your bow tie
你的领结
in the past, anyway,
可他们在拍摄过程中让你系的正规领带
But that regular tie they put you in for the filming --
对你也并没什么帮助
that wasn't doing you any favors, either.
我是说
I just mean...
那不像你
It wasn't you.
我正在安排后续采访的时间
So I'm, uh, scheduling these follow-up interviews now.
我能否给你个建议  还是继续用领结吧
But may I suggest...stick with the bow tie?
真不敢相信我会说出这种话
I cannot...believe I am saying that.
我会仔细考虑的
I'll take that under advisement.
我得  我得跟你谈谈
I need to, uh -- I need to talk to you...
关于咱们的片子  关于这份稿子
About our film... Uh, about, uh, this manuscript.
我想跟你谈  一种可能性
I want to talk to you about a -- well, a-a possible...
弗吉妮娅
Virginia?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在等赫伯
Uh, I'm waiting for Herb.
赫伯是谁
Who's Herb?
咱们的租户
Our tenant.
我的律师
My attorney.
你雇了赫伯·史普利博
You hired Herb Spleeb?
干什么
To do what?
把我丈夫想要的东西给他
Uh, to give my husband what he wants.
他想要什么
What does he want?
我们的孩子
Our kids.
乔治
George --
他认为我是个不称职的母亲
he wanted to put my fitness on trial,
要与我对簿公堂
as a mother.
他要让大家都知道
He -- he wanted to make it a matter of public record
我们的工作实质上淫乱不堪
the prurient nature of our work.
还有我在这里都干了什么  和你在一起时
And the hours I spend here and the hours I spend...
都干了什么
with you.
显然他的律师已经开始
Apparently, his lawyer had already begun asking questions
在公园广场酒店调查了
at the Park Plaza Hotel.
-乔治  -没错
- George. - Mm-hmm.
-乔治要这么做  -对
- George is doing this. - Mm.
意味着我们会有两次露面的机会
Meaning we would have had two debuts.
一边是CBS  我们将作为开创性的研究者
One on CBS, the two of us being introduced to the country
而被世人所认识  与此同时
as groundbreaking researchers, while at the same time,
某个法庭的法官将会向世界宣布
a judge in some court would also be presenting us
我们是一对道德沦丧
to the world as sleazy,
淫乱无耻的狗男女
amoral smut peddlers.
你不能让自己陷入那种境地
You -- you -- you cannot be put in that position.
弗吉妮娅  那样你根本没有机会胜诉
Virginia, that's -- that's completely untenable.
所以我们要这么做
So -- so what we do --
不  不  我已经解决了
No, no, no. It's already done.
赫伯这会儿正在向乔治提议
Herb is presenting an offer to George as we speak.
提出的条件对乔治来说非常有利
And the terms are very favorable to George.
只要他同意这事不上法庭就行
All he has to do is keep it out of court.
提议
An offer?
是的
Yes.
你不会
You haven't, uh --
你不会放弃了孩子的抚养权吧
You haven't given up your children, have you?
别这么说
Don't say it like that.
一旦影片播出后  我就能将他们夺回来了
But once the film airs, I will get them back.
弗吉妮娅  你不会真...
Virginia, you didn't do --
因为我会用这段影片证明这份工作
Because I will use the film to show that this work --
我对这份工作的付出是实实在在  值得尊重的
that my part in our work is respectable and legitimate
很快有一天  我会将他拉上法庭
And one day, very soon, I will drag him into court
然后利用CBS的盛誉
and I can use the sterling
将孩子们夺回来
reputation of CBS to get the kids back.
不  你不能...  你现在就得将他们夺回来
No, you cann-- no, you have to get them back now.
我做不到  这已成事实了
No. I can't. It's already done.
这只是暂时的
It's only temporary.
老妈
Hey, mom.
Mom.
你知道乔治·华盛顿特别喜欢狗吗
Did you know George Washington really loved dogs a lot?
而且他最喜欢的一只叫"甜嘴"
And his favorite one was named sweet lips?
我不知道呢
I didn't know that.
那你知道希腊曾经是一座岛吗
Did you know Greece was an island?
我也有个问题问你们
Ooh, here's my question for you.
你们爸爸和我一直在商量一件
Um, your dad and I were talking about something
你们或许会感兴趣的事
that you might think is fun.
去希腊吗
Going to Greece?
我想去看波托马克河
I want to go to the Potomac.
不是去希腊或者波托马克河
Not to greece or the Potomac.
但也算是一种全新尝试吧
But an adventure of sorts.
你们知道的  现在你们平时都待在这里
Do you know how -- how you spend all week here,
除了周三是在爸爸那边
except for Wednesdays, when you're with your dad?
然后周末的话
And then on the weekends,
你们是每隔一周就会和爸爸过周末
it's every other weekend with your dad?
还有奥黛丽
And Audrey.
我的问题是
Uh, well, my question is, uh...
你们都喜欢待在爸爸那边  对吧
Well, you like staying at your dad's place, right?
-没错  -特别喜欢
- Yes. - A lot.
这样的话  如果
All right, well, what if --
如果我们调换一下
what if we were to flip-flop it so...
你们平时待在爸爸那
you spend the week with him,
然后我每个周三接你们过来
And then you're here on Wednesdays with me,
还有每隔一周的周末也是
and then I-I would take every other weekend, just --
看看你们会不会喜欢这样的安排
just to see how it goes, see how we like it?
为什么
Why?
因为
Uh, because...
因为你们爸爸也想像我一样多点时间陪你们
Because your dad wants to spend as much time with you as I do.
没错  他是经常这么说
Yeah, he does say that a lot.
所以你们以后会更常见到他了
Yes, well, you would be seeing him a lot more.
仅此而已
That's all.
就跟现在的安排差不多  只是调换了一下
It would be pretty much the same, just...reversed.
我没意见
Okay.
但说了这么多  我们都快迟到了
But all this talking means we're gonna be late,
我今天可不能迟到
And I can't be late today.
是啊  而且你还穿着睡袍呢
Yeah. And you're still in your bathrobe.
弗吉妮娅
Virginia?
有什么事吗
Hello?
加州大学洛杉矶分校
在加州大学洛杉矶分校
...University of California at Los Angeles,
我们发现了一项不为人知
where behind closed doors, we have discovered
前所未有的研究正在进行
a groundbreaking study under way.
其中的惊人细节将在即将出版的
The surprising details of which will be revealed
充满争议的新书《男人与性》中
in a controversial, soon-to-be-published book
详细披露
called "Man and Sex."
几年前  我发现
I realized several years ago
人们不止忽略了对男性性行为
that not only has male sexuality been ignored
的科学研究
as a serious science,
整个人类性行为方向
But the field of sexuality, in general,
都仍是未涉足的领域
is also uncharted territory.
我跟你一样愤怒  弗吉妮娅
I am as furious about this as you are, Virginia.
相信我
Believe me.
我不明白
I-I don't understand.
真相残酷但简单
Well, it's painfully simple.
有人出卖了我们
Somebody has massively fucked up.
不是我
It wasn't me.
我的团队对保护客人隐私一事非常慎重
My team is meticulous when it comes to protecting my clients.
如果对手电视台有这种动作
And they would have been the first to hear
他们一定会是第一个收到风声的
about a potential scoop from a competing network.
我唯一知道的就是在这个四分钟影片里面
All I know is I've heard the word "Sex" Three times
"性"只出现过三次
in a four-minute story.
或许是你嘴巴不够牢  莱斯特
Well, maybe you were indiscreet, Lester.
所以这种事才会发生
Maybe that's how this happened.
我  怎么可能  你不能指责我...
Me?! Hell, no. You can make an ac--
我向你们保证
I assure you
这件事我一定会查个水落石出
that I'm gonna get to the bottom of this,
遗憾的是  尽管如此
despite the fact that, most regrettably,
这也无法改变CBS方面的决定
that's not gonna change the outcome with CBS.
他们本以为你们的故事会很有新闻价值
They thought they had something newsworthy with your story,
但如今被科夫曼博士抢先你们一步
but now with Dr. Kaufman beating us to the punch like this...
CBS已经来过电话了  他们不会...
CBS already called? They're not...?
我们的影片不会播出
Our piece is not gonna air.
...以及不必要的压力
...and unnecessary stress.
比尔  不
Bill, no.
看来科夫曼博士有合作伙伴
It seems Dr. Kaufman has a partner.
...比如说  男性如何感知与潜在对象
...Like, how does a male recognize chemistry
之间的火花
with a potential mate?
在进行性行为时
What kind of responsibility does the male bear
男性又需要背负哪些责任
with regards to sexual encounters?
在与男性的互动中
And there's also room to explore the role of women
女性的角色也同样值得探究
with regards to their interactions with men.
你认识那个年轻点的吗
Do you know the younger one?
他曾与我共事
He used to work with me.
弗吉妮娅...也认识他
Virginia also...knew him.
伊桑
Ethan --
怎么会  这一定都是我造成的
How -- how can that -- I must have caused this.
不是你造成的  弗吉妮娅
Virginia, you did not cause this.
我放弃孩子  为了什么
I let my kids go for that.
什么都不是
Noth-- for nothing.
那段影片也改变不了什么
The film wouldn't have changed anything.
-能改变的  -不
- Yes! Yes! - No.
-本来可以的  -你还不明白吗
- Yes, it would have. - Don't you see?
本来可以的
Yes, it would have.
我的孩子  我再也要不回他们了
My kids -- my kids -- they're gone.
我
I am...
我真的很抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
现在我们唯一能做的  就是继续研究
All we can do now I-is get back to work, okay?
所以我们要潜下心来
So we're gonna -- we're gonna put our heads down,
专心研究
And we're gonna work.
继续我们的研究  改变人类的研究
We're gonna do our work -- the work that matters.
这就是我们要做的
That's what we're gonna do.
我们继续研究
We're gonna get back to work.
朱莉娅
这才是颠覆人生的作品
Talk about life-changing.
安东尼奥尼真是
Antonioni is just...
阴暗
Grim.
诡异
Strange.
无法理解
Incomprehensible.
但真是个荡气回肠的爱情故事
But what a love story.
他们根本都不爱对方
They -- they barely even liked each other.
正是  这不是什么好莱坞童话
Exactly! It's not one of those Hollywood fairy tales.
没有什么"幸福地直到永远"
It's not "Happily ever after."
一切都如此真实复杂  如此...性感
It's real and complicated and very...sexy.
你不觉得吗
You didn't think so?
他们看对方的眼神  他亲吻她的方式
The way they looked at each other, the way he kissed her.
你以前就看过这部电影了
Y-y-you've seen this film before.
看过四遍
Four times.
所以  你是想让我从中悟出些什么吗
So...you wanted me to see something in it.
没错
Yes.
我想让你看清...我们
I wanted you to see...us --
一对真实  混乱  复杂的情侣
a real, messy, complicated couple,
但我们拥有那个
But a couple that has that.
那个是什么
That?
这个
This.
你能为了我不放弃这个吗
Will you not give up on this with me?
求你了
Please.
书的事还好办
Well, the book part was easy.
我给那伤透我女儿心的混球打了个电话
I called up that reprobate that broke my daughter's heart
说得很明白  这是他欠我的
and made it very clear he owed me one.
但把书交给竞争对手电视台
Getting the book to a competing network --
就得花一番功夫了
that, uh... took a little more doing.
你的关系网依然神通广大  巴顿
Well, you're still a connected man, Barton,
因为不管你做了什么
Because whatever you did,
如今我们的影片正式流产了
our film is now officially dead.
我还以为你看起来会更高兴呢  比尔
I thought you'd look happier about that, Bill.
这是你想要的  不是吗
It was what you wanted, wasn't it?
你打给我不就是为了这个吗
I mean, why you called me.
谢谢
Thank you.
我就直说了
All right, then.
你的研究远胜于科夫曼的  你很清楚
Your work is better than Kaufman's. You know that.
你只是还没准备好向世人展示罢了
You just aren't ready to show it to the world yet.
你用自己赌了一把
You bet on yourself.
我把弗吉妮娅也赌上了
I bet on Virginia, too.
我打电话给你时  我不知道
What I, uh -- what I didn't realize when I called you was...
弗吉妮娅正在与前夫争夺孩子的抚养权
...Virginia was in the middle of a custody dispute.
破坏影片这件事  你告诉过弗吉妮娅吧
You did tell Virginia you were killing the film.
我本来准备告诉她的
I-I was gonna tell her, of course.
我只是一直忙于制定对策
I was just, uh, setting the wheels in motion,
确保一切能按计划进行
getting all the -- the pieces in -- in place.
在你已经决定好
After you already decided
你要如何做之后吗
what you were going to do?
相信我  如果能收回我的选择  我一定...
Believe me, if I co-- if I could take it back...
你一定会这么做
You would.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
这让我想起你在妇产科医院时
That reminds me of when you wanted your study
为了你的研究所做的事
at Maternity Hospital,
你没有尽力说服我
And instead of trying to convince me
你是对的  而是威胁我
that you were right, you blackmailed me.
我这么说不是要责备你
I don't -- I don't say that to scold you.
但总这么一意孤行  不顾旁人
But blazing ahead like this -- always the one-man show,
只按自己的想法做事
always your terms and your terms only --
这会让你周围的人十分难过
Well, it's hell on the people around you
而且就我看来  你自己也不好受
and no picnic for you, either, as far as I could tell.
我知道这是什么感觉  比尔
I know what it's like, Bill,
生活在恐惧之中  不敢让别人进入内心
Living scared -- scared to let people in.
所以如今我过回了简单的生活
That's why my life is simple now.
在小诊所里做回普通医生  规律的工作
Being a doctor again, working at a clinic, steady routine.
我不是说一切都回复如初了
I'm not saying everything is fixed.
玛格丽特虽然没有离开我
I mean, Margaret hasn't left me,
但如今她只沉浸在自己的世界中
Although... what she does with her time...
我下了一个决心
But I took a leap of faith.
决定相信她
Decided to trust.
我告诉了她一切
I told her. Everything.
就算很艰难  但至少我们如今一起面对
As tough as it's been, at least we're in it together.
我从未想过...伤害弗吉妮娅
I-I never meant... to hurt Virginia.
不
No.
你从不是有意的
You never do.
我们不能这么继续下去
This has got to stop.
你知道的
You know that.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything.
不
Well, no.
这话不完全对
That's not entirely true.
我知道
I know...
我丈夫这么多年来一直有外遇
that my husband has been having an affair for years.
过去我总假装这不是真的
And I-I used to just pretend that it wasn't happening.
我假装视而不见
And then I looked the other way.
将心思都放在孩子们身上
And then I focused on my children.
然后  我遇见了你
And then...I met you.
我就知道
And I know...
我知道这...
I know that this...
我们之间的一切
thing that we have...
我知道这是我想要的
I know that I want it.
这点我知道
That is something that I know.
我想感受这一切
I know I want to feel.
车队刚刚到达首府
The motorcade has just arrived at the capitol
所有权贵已经聚集于此
where the attending dignitaries
准备参加总统就职典礼
have assembled for the inaugural ceremony.
如今正在就座的是肯尼迪家族
Now taking their seats are members of the Kennedy family.
肯尼迪夫人及其母亲...
Mrs. Kennedy with her mother...
卡路里燃烧弹
Cal-o-metric,
一天三粒  唤醒全新自我
Where the new you is just three small tablets away.
请稍候
Hold, please.
...当选副总统的林登·贝恩斯·约翰逊
Vice president-elect Lyndon Baines Johnson,
最后出场的是
and the last to take his place,
本届当选总统  约翰·菲茨杰拉德·肯尼迪
President-elect John Fitzgerald Kennedy.
瞧瞧
Look at that.
他居然不带礼帽
No top hat.
杜鲁门总统  尊敬的牧师
President Truman, reverend clergy,
各位公民
fellow citizens.
今天我们见证的
We observe today
不是政党的胜利  而是自由的胜利
not a victory of party but a celebration of freedom.
在此我向你们
For I have sworn before you
以及上帝
and almighty God
许下我们祖先170多年前
the same solemn oath our forebears prescribed
同样许下的神圣誓言
nearly a century and three-quarters ago,
这象征着结束  也是开端
symbolizing an end, as well as a beginning,
代表着更新，也是变革
signifying renewal, as well as change.
我们先辈为之奋斗的理念
For which our forebears fought
仍争议于世界每个角落
are still at issue around the globe --
那理念就是  人的权利
The belief that the rights of man
井非来自国家的慷慨
come not from the generosity of the state,
而是上帝的恩赐
but from the hand of god.
我们知道你们一定很失望
We know that we've failed you both --
你们向我们倾诉了经历的挣扎
that you've shared your struggles with us.
相信我们能研究出治疗方案
And trusted us to devise a-a treatment,
但我们却没有任何实质性进展
yet we made little discernable progress.
最糟糕的是
And -- and worst of all,
我们的尝试方式打击了你们
Our approach discouraged you,
让你们感到绝望
filled you with despair.
但我们不认为一切就该到此为止
But we don't think that has to be the end of the story.
我们已经研究出
We have developed --
正在研究一种治疗方案
are in the process of developing a protocol --
一种回到过去的方式
A path back, if you will --
遵照这些步骤
Steps that you can follow --
或许你们就可以找回幸福的生活
that may lead you back to a happy life,
完整而满足的生活
a full and satisfying life.
但重点是  这需要你们俩
But the key is, it takes both of you
下定决心
to make a leap of faith.
相信我们
Of trust.
一起努力
Working together.
共同进退
In it...together.
这是最重要的
That is the key.
今天  不要忘了
We dare not forget today
我们是第一次革命的继承者
that we are the heirs of that first revolution.
让所有的朋友与敌人都听到
Let the word go forth from this time and place
我此时此刻的这番话
to friend and foe alike...
革命的火炬已经传给了
that the torch has been passed
新一代的美国人
to a new generation of Americans --
生于这个世纪
born in this century...